{"Quiz": [
    {
        "1":
        {
            "id": "1",
            "question":"What is the purpose of the 'AndroidManifest.xml' file?",
            "answer":"To describe information about the app to the android build tools, android OS, and Google Play.",
            "options":[
                "It turns the mobile app into a web app.",
                "It makes the app have a responsive UI.",
                "To create the app.",
                "To describe information about the app to the android build tools, android OS, and Google Play."
            ]
        },

        "2":
        {
            "id": "2",
            "question":"How do we set an xml file from the 'layout' folder on display using Java code?",
            "answer":"Use the 'setContentView' method.",
            "options":[
                "Reference it in the 'AndroidManifest.xml' file.",
                "Use a 'System.out.print' statement.",
                "Use the 'findViewById' method.",
                "Use the 'setContentView' method."
            ]
        },

        "3":
        {
            "id": "3",
            "question":"What is the 'Intent' Java class used for?",
            "answer":"To initiate app operations.",
            "options":[
                "To create action-oriented event listeners.",
                "It asks the program what the user wants to do.",
                "To generate xml layouts.",
                "To initiate app operations."
            ]
        },

        "4":
        {
            "id": "4",
            "question":"What is the 'Toast' class used for?",
            "answer":"It creates a small display that shows the user a message without disrupting their app usage.",
            "options":[
                "To get a user to celebrate the app.",
                "It displays a piece of toast on-screen.",
                "Shows a message that the user must acknowledge before they can continue app usage.",
                "It creates a small display that shows the user a message without disrupting their app usage."
            ]
        },

        "5":
        {
            "id": "5",
            "question":"What is a fragment?",
            "answer":"An independent screen that can be hosted alongside other screens in an activity.",
            "options":[
                "A lost piece of app data.",
                "The glassy ook of an app icon.",
                "An activity.",
                "An independent screen, that can be hosted alongside other screens, in an activity."
            ]
        },

        "6":
        {
            "id": "6",
            "question":"What is the purpose of 'strings.xml'?",
            "answer":"It provides text for an application.",
            "options":[
                "It provides numbers for an application.",
                "It stores info on xml file hierarchies.",
                "It describes the types of thread used in sewing.",
                "It provides text for an application."
            ]
        },

        "7":
        {
            "id": "7",
            "question":"What is the purpose of 'styles.xml'?",
            "answer":"To format the appearance of a view, an activity, or the whole app.",
            "options":[
                "It holds fashion inspiration for fashion designers.",
                "It formats animations for activity widgets.",
                "It stores fonts to be referenced by 'strings.xml'.",
                "To format the appearance of a view, an activity, or the whole app."
            ]
        },

        "8":
        {
            "id": "8",
            "question":"What is the purpose of 'colors.xml'?",
            "answer":"It holds named references to color resources.",
            "options":[
                "To be a backup source of colors used in the app.",
                "To create a rainbow colored UI activity.",
                "It shows the color wheel.",
                "It holds named references to color resources."
            ]
        },

        "9":
        {
            "id": "9",
            "question":"Where do you find fragment resource xml files?",
            "answer":"app\\res\\layout",
            "options":[
                "app\\manifests",
                "app\\res\\values",
                "app\\java",
                "app\\res\\layout"
            ]
        },

        "10":
        {
            "id": "10",
            "question":"Where are the 'colors.xml', 'strings.xml', and 'styles.xml' files located?",
            "answer":"app\\res\\values",
            "options":[
                "app\\res\\drawable",
                "app\\res\\mimap",
                "app\\res\\xml",
                "app\\res\\values"
            ]
        }
    }
]}